Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
I have a question.
What’s going to happen to this world...
...while we try to keep our own lands
safe?
Everything is devestated.
Diseases.
Economic depressions.
Political reckonings.
People are restless.
Fearful and sad.
The army of justice did not show as much
struggle and courage...
... as the sons of the Devil.
The army of justice is conflicted.
And lost its sincerity.
The sons of Devil who found the lands
unprotected...
...has begun to attack to end humanity.
But...
...now the fire of justice...
...is lit again.
Our flags will flap...
...and world will find peace once again.
With the help of Allah, our people are
going to destroy the army of Devil.
It means we have already lost the war, if
we post our defending units in the Tent.
Our Alps will hold the surrounding four
hills.
In case of a sudden attack, our Alps will
go through the forest from the stream bed.
And help the Tent.
As you command, Gündüz Bey.
How is the situation in Söğüt, Bamsı Bey?
My Gündüz Bey, as you ordered, I have
engarrisoned Alps near Söğüt.
They are prepared for Balgay’s raid.
Thanks, Bamsı Bey.
At the top...
At the top of Crane and Hawk Hills,
we also engarrisoned Alps.
We will have no mercy on whoever
tries to come to Söğüt.
Thanks, Bamsı Bey.
By the way, Gündüz Bey...
…If Abdurrahman Ghazi already brought
Dündar Bey...
...we should start performing the
funeral prayer.
Abruhhaman Ghazi has not come yet,
Bamsı Bey.
What are you saying, Gündüz Bey?
He must have been here by now.
What if something happened to them?
I will go and ask the Alps.
My Bey...
...Alişar Bey is approaching to Tent
with Seljuk soldiers.
Only that dog’s head will get out of here.
My Batur.
Don’t leave me behind, my son.
Don’t leave, my lovely child.
Don’t leave me, my child.
Take me with you…
…take me with you, my son.
If Batur Brother had known that you
went to Mongols…
…asked for help from Balgay…
...would he even look at your face?
What would he say?
Shut up.
No, I will not shut up.
If you did not use Gündüz Bey as your toy…
…my brother would have been still alive.
My brother died because of you.
Because of you.
Even if you make me hush now,
what is going to change?
Shut up!
I said shut up!
Begone now!
I will make all of them pay for what they
did to us, my son.
If I am responsible for your death…
…may Allah take my life away.
I swear that I will take your revenge.
May dying be haram for me before I make
Osman regret the day he was born.
May it be haram, my son.
May it be haram.
I came to your Tent as a Bannerlord,
Gündüz Bey.
The person who killed my Alps…
…who made me get hit by an arrow.
Gündüz Bey!
Aren’t you that person, Alişar Bey?
Do you want me to show respect while
you stand in front of me...
... with a Mongol edict that
I don’t care about.
Alişar Bey!
This peltry once belonged
to Ertugrul Ghazi.
Letting somebody who cooperates with
Mongols sit on it does not suit us.
Oh, Allah!
In order to glorify your name,
I'm going towards my path with your name.
My head which raises against the tyrants,
will be only bowed for you.
I expect my desires to
happen only in your way.
Oh almighty, please help me with my war
against the heathens.
Don’t let me go away from your path.
Don’t mistake me with those ill-fated
heathens who run after reputation and fame.
Let me and my people be powerful and wise.
Let he who hears our name
feel safe and secure.
Let the tyrants who hear
our prayers be destroyed.
Amin.
Cruelty will end sooner or later.
The era is about to give birth
to a new resurrection...
...as long as you are awake.
As long as you are awake, son.
Whatever happens to Oguz only
happens while he is asleep.
Wake up, son.
Rise, son!
Let the justice walk when you walk.
Let the mercy smile when you smile.
Let the patience stand with you when you
resist against all the cruelties.
And let the people see the state in you.
That state should be such a state that...
... justice must be awakened with it and
the world of Islam must find comfort.
Tyrants must quiver with fear...
…and morals should rise once again.
But now the fire of justice is lit.
Our flags will flap, and the
world will retrieve peace once again.
With the help of Allah, our people
will destroy the army of Devil.
I came here as the person in charge of the
edict of almighty Mongol ruler, Geyhatu.
Both as a bannerlord…
…and a brother who knows
about all of the Tents.
We don’t have a brother who works
with the cruelties of Mongols.
When it comes to your Bannerlordship...
…as long as you are fair you will
face no trouble coming from us.
What’s your duty here?
Let’s talk outside as
calm as we are able to.
Geyhatu knows about everything.
He does not want any
troubles near the border.
What does he want then, Alişar Bey?
What does he want?
To surrender rabid dogs like Balgay?
Or to bow him and be silent
about his cruelties?
I want to keep Geyhatu away
from the borders, Bamsı Bey.
My duty here is taking Osman to Konya.
Geyhatu wants to learn about the Laws of
Genghis Khan and Balgay’s outcome.
Or else, he will come here in person.
If Geyhatu comes, all the Tents will miss
Balgay’s presence around here.
Alişar Bey…
…Osman is not here at the moment.
Even if he was here…
…neither your power nor Geyhatu’s
would be enough for taking him away.
The era of tyranny has come
to an end, Alişar Bey.
From now on, only our weapons will talk.
He who speaks with weapons will only
get hushed by weapons.
We fear nobody.
However, you should know that...
... Geyhatu is not happy with what
Balgay does these days.
I came here to do what Geyhatu desires…
… and to propose a deal.
Us, Kayıs, don’t like both flourished
words and men, Alişar Bey.
Tell us whatever you want to tell already.
Balgay will not stop as
long as he is alive.
We all know that very well.
Let’s fight against Balgay together.
The hostility between Balgay
and Geyhatu will make us stronger.
We share common interests.
Also may you not forget that
what goes around comes around.
Everybody leaves…
...Alişar stays.
Let’s say we agree with
your banner lordship…
…what are we going to get
in return, Alişar Bey?
Are you going to try killing me again...
...and trouble our Tent
with all kinds of disorders?
You would have been dead
already if I really wanted.
And you wouldn’t be standing in front me.
When it comes to your question, however…
…Kayı Tent will get what it desires.
And will be free do whatever
it wants to do with them.
Also nothing will happen to Osman.
What do you say, Gündüz Bey?
Bala, my daughter.
That impudent named Alişar is here again.
So I heard, my daughter.
I was about to go find out
why he came and what he wants.
I’m afraid he came back much
stronger than he was, Selcan Hatun.
He is gonna try to stick to
our collar even worse now.
Just as we were about
to get rid of Mongols.
I hope Gündüz does
not show his soft side to him.
Also, Osman is not here.
If we surrender to that kinless now, he
will become troublesome in the future.
Let’s go.
There is also something else.
What’s that, my daughter?
Perhaps, we can find a solution.
That impudent named Alişar...
... once asked for my father’s
permission to get married to me.
What are you saying, Bala?
- Doesn't Osman know about this?
- No.
Nobody does.
Please keep it as a secret.
Don’t you worry, my daughter.
I will not tell anybody.
It is good that you told me about this.
If Osman learns,
he will not let him live.
Even it means another
dirt would be removed from the world.
However, I fear something
bad would happen to Osman.
Let’s be patient, my daughter.
Let's go.
We will set the ambush
behind of Black Forest.
Is Balgay going to use that route?
Not Balgay…
…but the caravan that carries
the Byzantine Princess Adelfa.
My Bey, what business do we
have with the Byzantine Princess.
They want to make Adelfa and
Geyhatu get married
... so that they can
establish Byzantine-Mongol alliance.
We will prevent that.
My Bey, we are only two here.
- I will go to Tent and let the Alps know.
- No, Boran.
This mission is very important and secret.
We will handle it together.
As you wish, my Bey.
Your proposal sounds courageous.
Just like you my Bey.
Both your weapon and
your mind are skillful.
During hard times like this,
it is important to decide wisely.
We managed to defend
ourselves from the tyranny of Balgay.
But we have no problems with Geyhatu.
Gündüz Bey, the owner of the dog
should be found as guilty as its pet.
Geyhatu has lots of dogs.
Bamsı Bey, how can
we deal with all of them?
We are determined to pay taxes to Geyhatu,
and live a comfortable life, Alişar Bey.
This decision must be made
by all of the Beys.
We have lots of martyrs.
Our people are sick.
You can not decide by your
own like this, Gündüz Bey.
If you are the one who is the Bey
of Tent, go sit on that peltry.
If you are not, try to shut up
for a while, Bamsı Bey.
Once a Muslim is bitten by a snake...
...he can not get bitten again
by the same snake, Gündüz Bey.
They want to poison you.
Don’t you understand?
Osman has left to defend the Tent
against the anger of Geyhatu and Balgay.
As a Bannerlord, you are the only person
who can find out where he is.
Osman is not our problem anymore.
Alişar Bey said ‘’If Geyhatu comes,
you will miss Balgay.’’
Yet it’s the first day and
we already miss Dündar.
Gündüz Bey.
You can easily burn this Tent
with your unwise decisions.
You're making a big mistake.
Bamsı Bey doesn't know
much about politics.
Your job is hard, Gündüz Bey.
I have one more thing to say to you.
Bamsı Bey.
What is it Dumrul?
What's the hurry?
My Bey, Abdurrahman Gazi...
What about Abdurrahman Gazi?
We found him in the woods,
he's heavily wounded, my Bey.
Erkut Alp...
Abdurrahman Gazi, where is he?
My Bey, they put him in the sledge and
brought him to the medical tent.
- No, not the medical tent, Dumrul!
- My Bey, he's heavily wounded!
It's my Osman's command, don't you know?
There are Bey's that's loyal to Dündar...
... we can't know what they'll do!
Dumrul...
... until I say otherwise, everyone will
know Abdurrahman Gazi as dead.
We will treat him outside the Tent. Run to
the medical tent and get what's needed.
Then inform Gündüz Bey,
without that Alişar dog hearing it.
- Thank you.
- Come on, boy! Come on!
Come on boy.
Princess can't get to Konya.
No one from her convoy will survive.
Are we going to kill Princess too?
It's not like us to kill
an innocent woman.
If we can capture her alive, good.
But...
... if our mission is endangered,
you know what to do.
I know, my Bey. When the fire starts,
Allah doesn't pick trees.
Here they come, Boran.
My Bey, they're too little.
They trust themselves too much
when they are in their own land.
That's why they will get caught off guard.
Abdurrahman...
Abdurrahman, who did
this to you, brother?
Who did this to you, brother?
Open your eyes.
What will I say to my Ertuğrul Bey
if something happens to you, huh?
What will I say to my Ertuğrul Bey?
Open your eyes, brother, be strong!
He has a pulse, he's breathing,
he'll be okay, right Ayaz?
He has a pulse but it's slow, my Bey.
He had lost too much
blood when I found him.
You cauterized the wound,
the bleeding stopped!
Then why don't you open your eyes?
Open your eyes, brother!
Kılıç! How is Kılıç Alp?
Both Kılıç Alp and Abdurrahman
Gazi are strong, my Bey.
He is.
He is strong, he is Abdurrahman Gazi! He
is like a lion! My brother is like a lion!
But Erkut didn't make it, my Bey.
I know.
My Allah, My Great Allah...
The intention of the valiants who
pass away is your gratitude.
My Allah, may you...
... may you accept them in your place.
Accept them in your place.
They attacked them to get Dündar out.
Who could've done this, my Bey?
Ayaz, Ayaz...
Dündar is gone, Alişar is in the Tent.
Something is fishy here, Ayaz.
Everybody will know Abdurrahman
Gazi as dead until Osman comes.
- We will treat him here.
- As you say, my Bey.
Oh, my brother! Oh, my brother!
Come on, open your eyes.
Oh, great Abdurrahman Gazi.
Open your eyes, my valiant brother.
Now.
Allahu Akbar!
Princess.
Come outside.
You won't kill me, will you?
We've come here for life, not death.
And there's nobody here that can hurt you.
But I'm... I'm not the Princess.
What do you mean?
- Who are you?
- I'm...
It seems both you and the
Princess are in danger.
I will do whatever I can to save you.
Tell me, tell me who you are.
Who are you?
She's still alive, my Bey.
My condolences, Zöhre Hatun.
Thank you, Alişar Bey.
They took down my mountain, Dündar.
An ember burns where it falls, I know.
But what you need is
not anger, but strength.
We've discussed with Gündüz Bey.
I want to take you to my
mansion, if you want.
You will be comfortable in
the banner lord's mansion.
When our wounds heal, we will arrange
our cancelled marriage in a modest way.
You have my consent.
I want to get out of...
... this Tent that's
turned into a warzone.
Your anger and grudge is the
reason this Tent is restless.
Two lives were taken because of you.
Are you still not satisfied?
Selcan Hatun.
We know you, we know you very well.
Your life is full of squabble and words.
I understand that, but our wound is fresh!
Would you shut up? Shut up.
Stay away, Selcan Hatun!
The fire within me rises to my head!
Don't let my anger burn you!
I don't want to stay in the Tent
and get myself in trouble.
Since you are so kind,
you have my consent too.
We'll prepare and come to your mansion.
But...
... I won't leave my son here.
Gündüz Bey...
... allow me to bury him someplace
I want with my own hands.
Batur's death was not enough, now you
are trying to take him away from his home?
Aunt.
What a pity that you don't even
deserve your son's corpse.
You and Dündar are the
ones who brought this to us!
You killed your son! Now let him
sleep with his ancestors in his grave.
Aunt, I said!
Even if you are his mother,
Batur is Süleyman Şah's grandson!
His place is here.
No one will give you his corpse!
Enough!
Since when people say
something after Bey's words?
Don't you hear what she says?
They did all these games,
They allied with the Mongols and
attacked Osman in the Tent!
Selcan Hatun is right, Gündüz Bey!
We like guests when they
know their place, Bala Hatun.
Don't go too far!
Bala is my girl,
she's not a guest in the Tent.
And the things she said aren't lies!
When did you forget all these?
If Bala is your girl...
... then take your girl
and go to your tent.
Go!
Don't make me do
something I'll regret, aunt!
Alps!
Arrange a cart.
You will deliver Batur's
funeral to Zöhre Hatun.
If you are not Princess Adelfa...
... then where is she?
I can't tell you that!
We both know that Princess wouldn't
be a wife to a Mongolian bear willingly.
It doesn't matter! If not him,
someone else will take her!
We are Turk. We would
never hurt an innocent woman.
Remember how I treated you when
I thought you were the Princess.
I fear that she will get hurt!
If you don't tell me where
Princess is, then she will get hurt.
Because of you.
They will take Princess Adelfa...
... to Engürü road.
Please, treat her well.
Byzantine's games never end.
Neither our thirst for death!
Yes, my Bey!
This convoy was a trap
for precaution then.
But why did they do it?
We'll find out when they face us, Boran.
We will pass through the mountains
and go to the Engürü road.
This is the path they'll take.
We will make our ambush right there.
If one person survives,
Geyhatu will know it's us.
- And Princess?
- She will die too.
What is it Cerkutay?
You are sweating like an ox with a plow!
Osman is hunting Geyhatu's
soldiers that guard the cart.
Then there's no need for us to attack.
We will let Osman serve us.
Let him clean the scales,
then we will take the fish.
What does Osman want with the Princess?
It seems that the ones who gave
Osman Genghis Khan's Laws...
... now want the Princess.
Who does Osman work with,
Commander Balgay?
With the dark spirits,
don't you see?
We will let Osman do our job.
Then...
... we will take care of him.
Be ready, the spirits that left me
starting to get closer to me.
I feel it in my veins that
carry ember for blood!
Erlik Han, may happiness be yours...
... and blood be mine.
Are you ready, Commander Salvador?
We will go with 20 soldiers, Princess.
I will look for Osman's traces by
going to every secret place of his I know.
Maybe you'll find Osman himself
while you were looking for his traces.
If with God's help, I find
him, I will be honored...
to throw his corpse
to your feet, Princess.
How well he plays, while
looking at our eyes, traitor!
And we are watching him, Helen?
Is it bad?
Dündar Bey will take the Tent back.
Alişar is the banner lord like before.
So, Alişar will herd Dündar and
the other sheeps near him.
Since we have the Genghis Laws with us...
... we will herd Alişar.
Don't worry, Helen.
Fortune favors us.
We are slowly getting closer
to get rid of Osman!
Princess...
I haven't seen Master Yannis?
He went to the Margaret Monastery.
He gave you a mission.
A Byzantine Princess is on
the road from Nicaea.
Master Yannis was worried about her.
He wants you to...
... go after her with a special team.
Now...
... listen to my words carefully.
Listen carefully to what I'm gonna say.
My brave fellow.
My confidant.
My brother.
Abdurrahman Gazi.
The uncontrolled lion of the Kayı.
Stay strong, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Stay strong my brave man.
What's the news, Bamsi Bey?
Abdurrahman Gazi is my father's entrusted.
Kılıç is not just my helper.
He is my fellow, he is my confidant.
I know, Gunduz.
Gunduz.
Did Alisar become suspicious about it?
I don't think so.
Well done, son.
You've deceived this half breed
Mongol dog.
What Osman said came out right.
With the corpse of Dundar Bey, we see
those who got our father into trouble.
We learned to fight with perfidious...
...and clash with unbeliever...
...in your tent, Bamsi Bey.
I'm not regretful for all efforts
I spent on you, son.
I'm not.
You've gained my admiration.
From now on.
From now on, the end of the road
has appeared, son.
Alisar's life journey came to an end.
But, there will be a lot of foxes
around you.
In this hard time, as you want to take
Aygul and Zohre...
...Dundar Bey should be with Alisar.
My son.
We don't need suspicion but proof.
That's easy with the help of
Allah, Bamsi Bey.
I will send the soldiers to escort the
car carrying them.
We need to find Dundar Bey.
Long live with your wisdom, son.
Long live with your wisdom.
When the news we're waiting for
appear...
...and we find the trace of Dundar Bey...
...then it means Alisar will die.
My Gunduz.
We owe you running over the Alisar...
...under the stones of his mansion, son.
Maybe, it is our destiny.
We are deprived of both our tent...
...and our life.
We are worse than those who
we thought they were miserable.
May Allah give us power.
My Allah.
May Allah give us power...
...to bear this pain.
I wish I could say welcome cheerfully.
But, It didn't happen.
Those who come together in pain...
...connect each other stronger.
My home is your home.
It may not destroy your pain at all...
...but it'll relieve you.
Dundar Bey.
Father.
Father!
Father, We...
They couldn't, my daughter.
They couldn't.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here, my Aygul.
Your father is here.
Don't scare, my daughter.
Don't.
Alisar Bey....
...saved me from them.
They couldn't.
My husband..
Fortunately, you're alive.
You're here, my husband.
Batur.
My brave son.
My precious.
My son.
You're too young to die.
You're too young to fade away, my son.
Dundar Bey.
I will call those who did it to
you to account, my son.
I promise I will.
Don't worry about that, my son.
Don't.
I will take revenge from those
who killed you.
I will.
Thanks to me, Osman became the
enemy of your father.
Thanks to you. Dundar will be
the enemy of Osman.
They will shed each other's blood.
Then, Geyhatu will punish Balgay.
I will make all of my enemy fight
against each other.
We will take revenge surely.
We will surely catch those who
got us into this condition...
...and made us have this pain.
I could say how we will do this.
But Allah is great.
Now it's their turn to die.
Their turn, my daughter.
Their turn.
We'll stand against them rigidly,
Dundar Bey.
Now we have both the power
and the control.
We should bury him immediately.
I will bury my pain with my son.
But my anger is my dog.
My anger always will come with me.
From now on, they will see another
Dundar against them.
I will crush them like an insect.
I will crush them.
My son.
My brave man.
I promise I will crush all of
them like an insect.
Come this way.
Hurry! Let's go!
Don't stray from the troop.
I'm coming as well.
I need to deliver it to Bamsi Bey.
Wake up.
The rest is blessing.
Come on.
Look, Dundar bey.
Your son...
...who took all world against him for
the sake of the father of brave Batur...
We buried our son to here, Dundar Bey.
Ah! Ah!
You've been buried into a dark soil...
...without living your life to the
fullest, my son.
My son.
I wish those who killed you didn't stay
at peace in this world, my son.
My son!
You...
You the son of Suleyman Sah,
Dundar Bey.
Look around.
Look who is with you in your son funeral.
How many people are there?
The one who is buried is not only my son.
Osman buried your dignity into
this soil.
I promise on the corpse of my son...
...I will pull off the hands of Osman.
The kids who see what I will do him...
...will grow older with fear.
I will make a road from the heads of
people who support Osman...
...and I will walk over this road.
I will pile up the body of headless
people...
...and I will make a mountain from it
so that it will be a warning...
...for those who want to be forgiven.
A warning.
Come on, wife.
Come on.
We hit the jackpot this time, my bey.
I was so sorry for that girl.
I hope we'll save her.
I hope so, brother.
I hope so.
There isn't any place where Mongols
didn't torture.
We saw it again.
After you, princess.
We'll do it silently.
We will take the princess...
...after Byzantium soldiers disappear..
Be careful, Boran.
We don't know what we'll
encounter.
Don't worry, my bey.
-Dundar Bey.
Fortunately.
If we're alive, its thanks to Alisar.
He saved us from Osman.
Thanks.
Thanks, my bey.
Our friendship lasts forever.
But I am sorry that there are just
3 beys who are wise in the Kayı tents...
I'm sorry for that.
Now, you know me as dead.
The power is with Osman.
But with the help of Alisar....
...the bloody trap that they set up
will damage all of them.
You learned....
...and all living creatures who are
breathing will learn.
Whoever Alisar supports...
...the power is with him.
Osman.
He made Gündüz Bey sit on the throne.
We had to do it.
We kissed his hand.
He is no different than Osman.
What will we do now, my Bey?
Osman killed my son Batur and spilled
the blood of a brother.
There is no peace for us...
...before killing Osman...
...and those who stand before him.
But, my Bey...
We are low on force limits.
You either trust in your Bey...
...or you will stand beside Osman.
And if you trust in your Bey...
...you should listen to my
words carefully.
So, you are the new woman of Geyhatu.
We are returning to the Tent.
Hurry up, slackers.
We are under attack.
The princess is running away.
Orhan, go, I'll cover you.
Thank you, my Bey.
Come, Gündüz.
We'll do whatever necessary for them
to live, Bamsı Bey.
Not being able to take him to the Tent is
heavy, son.
Don't, Bamsı Bey. If we take him
to the oba...
...Alişar and Dündar Bey will find out
that we know everything.
I know, son. I know.
Any news from Alps?
We were right to doubt.
So, Dündar Bey fell to Alişar's trap?
My uncle thinks that Osman is the killer
of Batur.
And Alişar wants to use Dündar Bey's
grief of losing a child.
It was obvious from Alişar's venomous
snake-like behaviours.
He sends Dündar after us, so he can wash
his dirty works with the blood spilled.
But, son, if he planned such a ruse...
...he'll need support from the Tent.
And the wells that will provide to
Alişar's tent is obvious.
Ayaz.
Yes, my Bey.
You'll watch Demirci Bey and Şahsin Bey
closely.
You'll follow their every step and
every person they speak to.
If you get suspicious of anything
send word to me.
Yes, my Bey.
Son,
I'm grieved but only for the situation
of Dündar Bey.
Now, when you learn the truth,
how will he look into our faces?
We have to save Dündar Bey from the
hands of this snake, Bamsı Bey.
And to do this...
...we have to crush the nest of the snake.
I'm sorrowful, Dündar Bey.
We lost our child...
We lost our home...
We lost our Tent...
What else can Osman do to us?
Ahh, Osman.
One who calls his madness, bravery.
One who acts on his will...
...and call it law.
They think the fields are theirs now.
Let them think.
Let them enjoy it.
Then, I'll be onto them with
all my fury.
And I'll make his followers regret
what they did.
We lost everything.
How will we breathe easy?
How will these things happen?
What are you planning, my Bey?
Time of that will come, too, Hatun.
For now, what is important for us...
...is Alişar Bey.
We'll triumph because of him.
Dündar Bey, Alişar Bey wishes to see
you in the yard.
This...
This will be your last
crying, inshallah.
They took our child but...
...they won't take our home.
How will you explain to my father that
you are working with the Mongols.
Let's see what will he do when he
finds out.
Aygül...
I feel down in the mouth.
I can't take on with you.
Get out of my sight!
Mother, this can't be.
Tell my father, he needs to know.
Don't advise me, Aygül.
You take care of yourself,
that's enough for me.
We've seen what you did when
you knew a lot.
My father will learn soon.
If not today, then tomorrow.
If you don't tell him...
What do you want from me, Turk?
No need to be afraid, Princess Adelfa.
I came to save you from being
a concubine to Geyhatu.
I don't believe you.
Calm down, Hatun.
I didn't come here to hurt you.
But to have you as a guest.
What do you want from me?
Preventing your marriage with Geyhatu.
Are you ready for the big day, Dündar Bey?
Till the unrest of Osman ends...
...blood that will be spilled is halal
to me, Alişar Bey.
Gündüz sieged everywhere with his alps,
Alişar Bey.
It will be a hard battle.
Before the sun sets, warriors
of Geyhatu...
...will be under my command.
We aren't alone.
Be at ease.
You can't even imagine...
...how much Geyhatu trusts me.
Dündar Bey.
The blood that will be spilled...
...when your loyal alps and Beys
see you...
...will be the end of the Osman calamity
that hurts your Tent like a plague.
Alps on Söğüt and on patrol are on me.
Don't worry.
Those who crushed the succession
my brother gave to me...
...will be crushed under my boots.
It's the time of vengeance, Alişar Bey.
I'll be in your debt for the
rest of my life.
Not at all! I've done my duty
for these lands.
I'm grateful to you.
If it wasn't for a shrewd Bey like you...
...there would be nothing left from the
Kayı Tent, other than good memories.
And valiant people without graves...
Your child, valiant Batur...
...I wish he could be by your side
on this sacred day.
I don't want Süleyman Şah's bloodline
to end with you...
Zöhre Hatun can't give you another
child, anymore.
But I'd like to find a Bey daughter
who will continue your bloodline.
The one who will continue the bloodline
of my father Süleyman Şah...
...is my son Bahadır, who I once exiled
because of Osman.
Bahadır, you say?
I learned that you have another child.
That relieved me.
May Allah look after your son.
Why are you doing this?
Mongols are our common enemy.
Isn't it enough?
I can't go back to Constaninople.
We'll guest you at the Tent,
until things turn back to normal.
Then, you can go anytime you want.
I've been thinking of killing myself,
for days.
How weird is that I'll survive with the
helping hand of the Turks I hate.
Hatun...
Don't bow down to anyone but the creator.
May God protect you, Turk.
I found tracks. They went this way!
My Bey, I hear their voices.
-Look everywhere!
- They are coming.
Nobody knows we are here.
Balgay...
If we go together, we'll give them what
they want. They'll capture us.
-Take the princess to the Tent.
-My Bey.
Go.
As you wish, my Bey.
Come on.
Balgay...
Come to me...
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim...
What's happening Akça?
You look sorrowful.
You look abstracted.
I listen to my inner voice, Sheikh.
We came here to wait for our Âhi brothers.
Most of the friends at the Söğüt
are broken.
We couldn't find a home.
I know that despair doesn't fit your tent.
But because of the trouble, we were
dealing with...
...I'm very uncomfortable.
On the 214th verse of Bakara,
Allah says...
...Muslims, did you think that...
...you can go to heaven before
experiencing...
...the likes of things...
...the ones before you experienced?
Earth is the house of troubles...
...and the grave of the living.
The world is a place of trial, Akça.
It takes patience...
It takes gratitude...
It takes reasoning and resignation.
In here, you will ask Allah's mercy...
...so that you won't have to ask
it from people.
This world is a delusion, Akça.
As long as you don't forget the delusion,
you can't remember the truth.
Where is the princess?
I see that your power can
only match women.
Come and fight me like a soldier.
If you want to see a soldier...
Come, Osman...
Seize him.
Comparing to what Muslims
lived trough in our prophet's time...
...what trouble is ours?
That discrimination...
These years of grieving...
After the emigration of Muslims
to Ethiopia...
...polytheist had done everything
to Muslims.
They stopped every kind of trade...
...even marriages with them.
This took three long years.
Sufferings... Troubles... Poverty...
Continued by growing even more,
day by day.
Believers had to eat barks and leafs
to not starve...
Cries of little children could be
heard from long distances.
Just when they thought it was over,
other bad things happened.
Our Prophet's uncle, Ebu Talib and
his wife Hadradth Hatice passed away.
Just when they thought attacks
were over, it increased.
Allah's messenger...
...went to his relatives, to Tahif...
...by taking his adopted child
Zeh bin Hares with him.
But troubles found our master in there,
as well.
First, they mocked him...
...then, they stoned him.
Even if the ones on the ground
had let it happen...
...the ones on the sky did not.
Angel Gabriel came down...
..'' O' messenger of Allah, what do you
want me to do?''
''Ask it, and I will crush these two
mountains on their heads'' he said.
The prophet of mercy said no.
No...
''I want their generations to
have believers...
who don't go against the words of Allah.''
he said.
Oppression was more than words
could handle...
...a word from Medina...
...became a cure for wounds...
...a relief for hearts.
While polytheists were trying to finish
off Muslims with great effort in Mecca...
The people at Medina were becoming
Muslim.
They invited the Prophet of Mercy
to Medina.
In a short time, there wasn't a house
that Islam hadn't entered.
Then...
Then, believers conquered Mecca.
Summary is...
The end of a night is a morning...
...the end of winter is summer...
...and the end of a slope is a flatness.
Those who aren't patient to trouble...
...can't reach happiness.
Thank you, my Sheikh.
Thank you.
Aslı and Kerem.
I've put a great effort.
It's finally over.
I'll ask you for marriage
when my father comes back.
My daughter, having a baby
isn't destined for you.
I don't know if it ever will.
Miracles are owned by Allah.
Our Sare mother became a mother
when she was 90 years old...
Maybe, a woman whose womb was
splintered can be a mother too.
You always run away.
You ignore me. It's not going to be
like that, Bala.
Find another woman for yourself. I'm not
good for you.
A child is a gift of Allah. A dagger
wound can't separate us when...
we like each other that much.
Osman, don't.
I can't. You'll have kids.
- I'm not good for you.
- Are you?
Bala, I'm falling apart without you.
Being without you is the biggest obstacle
between me and my tomorrow.
You're the power, Bala.
You're the strength and the
light of my way.
You're my dream, my love.
My biggest dream is to marry you after
receiving my Sheikh's consent.
You're my love, Hatun.
If Allah doesn't give us children...
I'm fine with that.
I'm fine with everything
when I'm with you.
Tell me.
Are you fine with that?
I'm fine with everything
when I'm with you, Osman.
I've waited much to kill you, Osman.
The spirits are telling me that...
"You wanted, we gave Osman to you."
But Erlik han doesn't want your life.
He wants your weapon.
In this mighty way of Cengiz Han,
we are in the same way, Osman.
Untie him.
As I see, you don't want
Princess Adelfa....
to marry Geyhatu.
What do you want from me? I want to...
fight with a brave man like you, Osman.
I told you that my weapon isn't for sale!
Sure I know I can't buy you by offering
post or gold.
So why do you want my alliance?
Give him.
I would take your life if I wanted to,
Osman.
You defeated me, and you are defeated
by Geyhatu.
What do you mean?
Speak directly.
Nobody knew where Princes Adelfa was going
except for Geyhatu and Byzantine Emperor.
I see that you also knew.
Somebody gave you that information.
I don't know who did it, but I know why,
Osman.
If Geyhatu had married Princess,
it would end Turks.
They gave you that information to
prevent this.
I don't know who did it, Osman Bey.
Only thing I know is we are in the same
path, Osman Bey.
I prefer death to be with you.
Would you? Even if Geyhatu sent a army
to your tent to destroy your brother?
My condolences to you, Aygül Hatun.
May he rest in peace.
Amin.
My brother is gone, but my father is here.
Thanks to you.
May Allah be pleased with you.
You have another trouble, Aygül Hatun.
No.
Isn't that enough?
Unfortunetaly, I heard you while I was
going to my room to take a book.
I couldn't help but overhear what
Zöhre Hatun did.
You are in a bad situation, I know.
It's family issues. It would be better
if you hadn't heard, Alişar Bey.
However you like, I didn't hear,
and you didn't speak.
I didn't hear,
Even, you didn't know this.
Why?
My mother did wrong.
My father needs to know.
How can I hide this?
I am thinking, though. I don't know how
my father will react if I speak.
I am afraid.
Just wait.
Wait and see, Aygül Hatun.
You need to think over the things
that will effect your life.
You need to learn how to
ignore your feelings.
Wait and see.
- But...
- You were born as a daughter of Bey.
And a bannerlord is in love with you.
If Allah permits, and
you become my wife...
You will be in a much bigger
policy.
You'll have much more power.
Don't do anything until you...
have that power.
Just let it be.
And then, you can do whatever you want
to do.
Also, anger doesn't looks good in you,
Aygül Hatun.
You need to smile, flowers...
and have jewelry.
In my mansion, being happy is
connected with being silent.
I know, what you want to tell your
father is important for you.
But, it is not the right time.
I accept your gift, Alişar Bey.
I am listening.
Dündar Bey is still alive.
-How do you know?
-I've spies in Söğüt and Konya, Osman Bey.
Geyhatu wants Cengiz Han's laws
and his dagger.
Just like you.
You hate me, but you know I can
face you in war, like a man
However, Geyhatu isn't like me.
He tricked both of us.
Alişar turned out to be Geyhatu's spy.
What do you mean?
Geyhatu gave Alişar bannerlordship.
A huge army is going to Söğüt tonight.
Cengiz Han's laws is only thing he wants.
Wait, don't get angry now.
I didn't finish.
Do you know where Dündar Bey is now?
In Alişar's hand.
He want to destroy my brother and get
Dündar in the lead.
It was him who shot my uncle
while we were fighting.
Your uncle.
and Batur.
Gündüz Bey, Alişar Bey invited you to
the mansion.
Give him my blessings, Zorba.
Accepting the invitation is sunnah.
I will come before it gets dark.
Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
If you go, they will kill you, son.
I know, Bamsı Bey.
So, you are not going, ha?
You gave me that advice in the
Alp class, Bamsı Bey.
"If you don't face the trouble,
it gets bigger...
you need to face it...
- Either it takes you down, or you do.
Eyvallah, son.
Than it is time to fight.
Listen to me, Bamsı Bey.
Thank Allah, you are better, my Bey.
I will get better to take revenge for
my son, Saltug.
Revenge is for valiants.
Today, we take revenge.
Aygül.
My father needs to know what you did.
Is there any news about Osman?
No. However, inshallah he will see
you in the charge when he comes.
I can't be sure about anything before
Osman dies, Saltug.
I know, my Bey, I know.
It's Osman's end.
Geyhatu sent a huge army.
They will be here before it gets dark.
Alişar Bey sent Zorba to Gündüz.
He invited him to his mansion.
When Gündüz comes, he will be
punsihed, and the tribe will be mine.
Today, we call acount, Saltug.
No one could stop it.
Father, I have something to tell you.
Geyhatu wanted to impose a tax on Byzantine
and get gold with this marriage.
And you wanted to destroy Byzantine
and get gold...
with Cengiz Han's laws' power.
Cengiz Han says: there is only one
power that unites two opponents.
The benefit.
Where your Alp take Princess to?
Somewhere secure.
Are you looking for trouble by keeping
that woman alive, Osman?
Mercy is no good, don't you know?
What about Alişar?
His friendship with Sofia,
His interest in trading,
Geyhatu wanted these.
Until I came and send Alişar to Konya.
Damn that day I sent him!
I sent him to Konya instead of killing
him!
That was the most stupid thing I have
ever done.
My uncle thinks I killed Batur.
That's why they will kill first Gündüz,
then Samsa Bey and Bamsı Bey.
At the end, you.
Your sword is ready, your
horse is ready.
If you want to, go to your tent.
But, when you go, you'll see Gündüz,
Bamsı Bey and Samsa Bey are dead.
You'll see Alişar as the bannerlord and
Dündar Bey in your father's throne.
Or, we both take what we deserve and
go on.
Either be with me and fight Geyhatu, Alişar,
Dündar.
Or go to your tent and die.
Your choice, Osman.
It's a deal, Balgay.
I am with you.
May our alliance be good.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com